footballoutsiders.com 2019-04-18

# Privacy Policy | Football Outsiders

Last modified: January 23, 2019

### Introduction

EdjSports, LLC (“EdjSports,” “our”, “we”, or “us”) respects your privacy and is committed to protecting it through our compliance with this policy.  
This policy describes the types of information we may collect from you or that you may provide when you visit the website [www.footballoutsiders.com](http://www.footballoutsiders.com/ "www.footballoutsiders.com") (our “Website”) and our practices for collecting, using, maintaining, protecting, and disclosing that information.

This policy applies to information we collect:

  * On this Website.

  * In email and other electronic messages between you and this Website.

It does not apply to information collected by:

  * Us offline or through any other means, including on any other website operated by EdjSports or any third party (including our affiliates and subsidiaries); or 

  * Any third party (including our affiliates and subsidiaries), including through any application or content (including advertising) that may link to or be accessible from or on the Website.

Please read this policy carefully to understand our policies and practices regarding your information and how we will treat it. If you do not agree with our policies and practices, your choice is not to use our Website. By accessing or using this Website, you agree to this privacy policy. This policy may change from time to time. Your continued use of this Website after we make changes is deemed to be acceptance of those changes, so please check the policy periodically for updates. 

### Children Under the Age of 13

Our Website is not intended for children under 13 years of age and we do not knowingly collect personal information from children under 13. If we learn we have collected or received personal information from a child under 13 without verification of parental consent, we will delete that information. If you believe we might have any information from or about a child under 13, please contact us at [techsupport@footballoutsiders.com](mailto:techsupport@footballoutsiders.com).

### Information We Collect About You and How We Collect It

We collect several types of information from and about users of our Website, including information:

  * by which you may be personally identified, such as name, postal address, e-mail address, telephone number or any other information that is defined as personal or personally-identifiable information under an applicable law ("personal information");

  * that is about you but individually does not identify you, such as your response to online surveys; and/or

  * about your internet connection, the equipment you use to access our Website and usage details.

We collect this information:

  * Directly from you when you provide it to us.

  * Automatically as you navigate through the site. Information collected automatically may include usage details, IP addresses, and information collected through cookies and other tracking technologies.

  * From third parties, for example, our business partners and service providers.

### Cookies and Similar Technologies

The Website may use technologies such as cookies, beacons, tags and scripts. These technologies are used for a variety of purposes, such as analyzing trends, administering the Website, analyzing how users interact with the Website, and gathering demographic information. By using the Website, you consent to our use of cookies and similar technologies. 

Users can control the use of cookies at the individual browser level. If you reject cookies, you may still use our Website, but your ability to use certain features may be limited. To learn how you can manage your Flash cookie settings, visit the [Flash player settings page on Adobe's website](https://helpx.adobe.com/flash-player/kb/disable-local-shared-objects-flash.html). 

We may use analytics software to allow us to better understand the functionality of our Website. This software may record information such as how often you use an application, the events that occur within the application, aggregated usage, performance data, and where an application was downloaded from. 

### Information You Provide to Us

The information we collect on or through our Website may include:

  * Information that you provide by filling in forms on our Website. This includes information provided at the time of registering for an account, subscribing to our premium subscription service, posting material, or requesting further services. We may also ask you for information when you choose to participate in surveys sponsored by us and when you report a problem with our Website.

  * Records and copies of your communications (including email addresses), if you contact us.

  * Details of transactions you carry out through our Website, including details relating to the placement and fulfillment of your orders. You may be required to provide financial information before placing an order through our Website.

  * Your search queries on the Website.

You also may provide information to be published or displayed (hereinafter, "posted") on public areas of the Website, or transmitted to other users of the Website or third parties (collectively, "User Contributions"). Your User Contributions are posted on and transmitted to others at your own risk. Please be aware that no security measures are perfect or impenetrable. Additionally, we cannot control the actions of other users of the Website with whom you may choose to share your User Contributions. Therefore, we cannot and do not guarantee that your User Contributions will not be viewed by unauthorized persons.

### Third-Party Information Collection

Some content or applications, including advertisements, on the Website are served by third-parties, including advertisers, ad networks and servers, content providers, and application providers, who use tracking technologies to collect information about you when you access and use our Website or visit third-party sites. The information they collect may be associated with your personal information or they may collect information, including personal information, about your online activities over time and across different websites and other online services. They may use this information to provide you with interest-based (behavioral) advertising or other targeted content.

We do not control these third parties' tracking technologies or how they may be used. For information about how you can opt out of receiving targeted advertising from many providers, see Your Choices About Our Use of Your Information. If you have any questions about a third party’s practices, you should read the third party’s privacy statement or contact the third party directly. 

### How We Use Your Information

We use information that we collect about you or that you provide to us, including any personal information:

  * To present our Website and its contents to you.

  * To provide you with information, products, or services that you request from us.

  * To manage your account and/or subscription, including expiration and renewal notices. 

  * To fulfill any other purpose for which you provide it.

  * To carry out our obligations and enforce our rights arising from any contracts entered into between you and us, including for billing and collection.

  * To notify you about changes to our Website or any products or services we offer or provide though it.

  * To send you communications that we believe may be of interest to you, including information about our own products, services, news, events, promotions, or special offers. 

  * To send you communications that we believe may be of interest to you, including information about our own and third-parties’ products, services, news, events, promotions, or special offers. 

  * In any other way we may describe when you provide the information.

  * For any other purpose with your consent.

In addition, the information we collect automatically helps us to improve our Services and to deliver a better and more personalized service, including by enabling us to:

  * Estimate our audience size and usage patterns.

  * Store information about your preferences, allowing us to customize the Services according to your individual interests.

  * Speed up your searches.

  * Recognize you when you use the Services.

### Disclosure of Your Information

We may disclose aggregated information about our users, and information that does not identify any individual, without restriction. In addition, we may disclose personal information that we collect or you provide:

  * To our subsidiaries and affiliates.

  * To contractors, service providers, and other third parties we use to support our business operations.

  * To a buyer or other successor in the event of a merger, divestiture, restructuring, reorganization, dissolution, or other sale or transfer of some or all of EdjSports’ assets, whether as a going concern or as part of bankruptcy, liquidation, or similar proceeding, in which personal information held by EdjSports about our Website users is among the assets transferred.

  * To fulfill the purpose for which you provide it. 

  * For any other purpose disclosed by us when you provide the information.

  * With your consent.

We may also disclose your personal information:

  * To comply with any court order, law, or legal process, including to respond to any government or regulatory request.

  * To enforce or apply our Terms of Use and other agreements, including for billing and collection purposes.

  * If we believe disclosure is necessary or appropriate to protect the rights, property, or safety of EdjSports, our customers, or others. 

### Your Choices About Our Use of Your Information

We strive to provide you with choices regarding the personal information you provide to us. We have created mechanisms to provide you with the following control over your information: 

  * Tracking Technologies and Advertising. You can set your browser to refuse all or some browser cookies, or to alert you when cookies are being sent. To learn how you can manage your Flash cookie settings, visit the Flash player settings page on Adobe's website. If you disable or refuse cookies, please note that some parts of this site may then be inaccessible or not function properly.

  * Third Party Information Collection. We do not control third parties' collection or use of your information to serve interest-based advertising. However, these third parties may provide you with ways to choose not to have your information collected or used in this way. You can opt out of receiving targeted ads from members of the Network Advertising Initiative ("NAI") on the NAI's website at <http://www.networkadvertising.org/>. 

### Accessing and Correcting Your Information

You can review and change your personal information by logging into the Website and visiting your account profile page.

You may also send us an email at [techsupport@footballoutsiders.com](mailto:techsupport@footballoutsiders.com) to request access to, correct or delete any personal information that you have provided to us. We cannot delete your personal information except by also deleting your user account. We may not accommodate a request to change information if we believe the change would violate any law or legal requirement or cause the information to be incorrect.

If you delete your User Contributions from the Website, copies of your User Contributions may remain viewable in cached and archived pages, or might have been copied or stored by other Website users. Proper access and use of information provided on the Website, including User Contributions, is governed by our Terms of Use. 

### Your California Privacy Rights

California Civil Code Section § 1798.83 permits users of our Websites that are California residents to request certain information regarding our disclosure of personal information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes. To make such a request, please send an email to [techsupport@footballoutsiders.com](mailto:techsupport@footballoutsiders.com)  
or write us at: EdjSports, 732 E. Market Street, Louisville, KY 40202.

### Data Security

We have implemented measures designed to secure your personal information from accidental loss and from unauthorized access, use, alteration, and disclosure.  
The safety and security of your information also depends on you. Where we have given you (or where you have chosen) a password for access to certain parts of our Website, you are responsible for keeping this password confidential. We ask you not to share your password with anyone. 

Unfortunately, the transmission of information via the internet is not completely secure. Although we do our best to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee the security of your personal information transmitted to our Website. Any transmission of personal information is at your own risk. We are not responsible for circumvention of any privacy settings or security measures contained on the Website.

### Changes to Our Privacy Policy

It is our policy to post any changes we make to our privacy policy on this page. If we make material changes to how we treat our users' personal information, we will post the new Privacy Policy on this page with a notice that the Privacy Policy has been updated.

You are responsible for ensuring we have an up-to-date active and deliverable email address for you, and for periodically visiting our Website and this privacy policy to check for any changes.

### Contact Information

To ask questions or comment about this privacy policy and our privacy practices, contact us at: 

Mail: EdjSports, 732 E. Market Street, Louisville, KY 40202  
Phone: 502-208-4088  
Email: [techsupport@footballoutsiders.com](mailto:techsupport@footballoutsiders.com)

### Terms of Use

To see our Terms of Use, please click here.
